A way far away, who shall arrive?
A way with countless troubles, who shall achieve?
Please contact us for any inquiries: turkision@gmail.com
Mother!
-Mother!
-My Halime...
My beautiful daughter...
I arrived, my daughter. I am here.
Did you get cold, my beautiful daughter? Wait...
-Mother?
-Wait, your mother will warm you up now.
My beautiful daughter...
-My Halime..
-Mother...
My beautiful daughter,
do you feel warm now?
-Halime died, mother.
-Sleep, my daughter... Sleep.
Mother, don't you see me?
-Sleep, my daughter...
-Mother!
I arrived...
-Don't be scared, my angel...
-Halime died!
Halime died...
Don't you die too, mother, don't die!
Mother! Mother!
Mother open your eyes! Mother!
Mother! Mother! Mother!
Mother! Halime!
Halime...
Brother... brother? Brother!
It was a nightmare. It was a nightmare brother.
Drink some water.
In the name of Allah,
the compassionate, the merciful.
Did you see my mother Bala again?
I miss her, my sister.
-I missed her so much.
-I can see that, brother.
I can see that, brother.
I can see your pain.
I miss my mother Bala too.
And my sister...
Halime... Whenever I hear her name,
my heart hurts, brother.
-Brother...
-My Fatma... my sister...
-My sister...
-But I cannot do anything...
My Shahzade(Prince)!
Let us train together, shall we?
Come, Konur Bey.
The field is yours!
Let's go my Shahzade(Prince)!
You know what to do!
Hit! Hit! Hit!
My Shahzade(Prince)! Come on!
Hit! Hit! Hit! Hit!
What happened, my Shahzade(Prince)?
What happened? Was it too strong?
Control your anger. It weakens you.
-Come on my Shahzade(Prince)!
-Come on, brother! You can defeat him!
I am not my anger's servant...
..I am its master!
Come on my Shahzade!
Experience always defeats talent.
You're right, but...
...precaution always defeats experience.
It was you who told me to
always have a secret dagger, Konur Bey.
Yeah.
-You've become a brave Bey, my Shahzade
-Thank you.
My Shahzade(Prince)... Konur Bey.
-The army came to Yenisehir for the conquest.
-Good.
Oh Bursa..
They trust the castles around them...
...and they boast about themselves.
Kite...
Atranos...
and...
Kestel.
When these castles fall,
who can protect Bursa from us, Osman Bey?
No one! And they know that.
Therefore, they are trying to attack us
to harm our union.
They wanted to attack Yenisehir
but they paid its price with their lives.
Giving their lives won't be enough
to pay that price...
...we will also take their castles.
-Sure we will.
Whenever there is a fight,
my heart is divided into 3 pieces.
My Orhan, my Alaeddin grew up
and they became strong Beys.
I know that if we have one of them,
we will achieve our goal if Allah permits.
We will. We will.
O, Bursa... It's either you...
...or me.
Alps! In order!
Praise be! Praise be!
Our target is Kestel Castle.
My Alps!
-Are you ready for the fight?
-We are, my Bey!
-What do Alps want?
-To fight!
-What else?
-The blood of infidels!
-They want the innocent ones to be in peace!
-What else?
-To be martyrs!
O praise be to my valiants!
Praise be!
I brought news from Konya, Boran Bey.
Thank you, brother.
My Bey, it's from Konya.
No.
Beys.
Everyone come to the council. Now!
Ulgen Hatun, I was looking for you.
My mother wants to see you.
Fatma, they say a messenger came.
Any news from Cerkutay?
No. No, sister Ulgen.
-The messenger came from Konya.
-It's been so long... Without him.
But I know he's not dead.
Cerkutay would never die.
Mother! My father is back, right?
My father is back home! He's back, right?
-He will be back, my dear.
-When, mother?
You keep saying he'll come back.
But he doesn't come back.
He'll come back, my dear.
My Beys, I'm stopping
the conquest of Kestel.
Why are you stopping it, my Bey?
Our people need a new Sultan now.
-How come, my Bey?
-Sultan Mesud...
...got poisoned.
And there is no going back.
Oh no.
This means the horses will whinny again.
Yes. The swords will be drawn.
And many men will die until
the new Sultan ascends the throne, huh?
Now tell me...
Shall we put ourselves in for the position?
My Allah is my witness that
my heart wants it.
Well, my Bey Osman deserves
to be the head of all Turkmen.
But we should know our place, my Bey.
On one side, Germiyan even stronger than Konya.
On the other side, other beylics.
-You say our power isn't enough for our dreams?
-Boran Bey, you're right. But we know this.
-The less have can still win against the more.
-Konur Bey, I see you.
You're absolutely right.
But even if all of us gather...
...we can recruit 10.000 horsemen at most.
Germiyan can gather 100.000 horsemen with a call.
Karesi is about to capture Constantinople
with their ships.
Karaman, right beside Konya,
is waiting for their prey to fall down.
Tell me, Bayindir Bey.
What should we do?
My Bey, we should ally with Germiyan.
Even... Forgive me, my Bey, but...
-We should enter Germiyan's service.
-Stop there.
-What are you saying, Bayindir Bey?
-Konur Bey.
Many states and beylics have got
destroyed like untimely dreams.
I thought we agreed before.
But what about entering someone's service?
Beys, this is the council of advice.
Everyone can express their opinions here.
Just let his words come out of his mouth.
Speak, Bayindir Bey.
Alps, tell stablemen to prepare
the horses of shahzades(princes).
As you order, Malhun Hatun.
-Tell the ones in the soup kitchen to prepare food.
-As you order, Malhun Hatun.
Mother, what is this preparation for
before the council is over.
Did father give an order?
No need for an order for this, daugter.
I'm his wife for years. I know your father well.
-As far as I know, it will be a long day.
-Malhun Hatun.
Shall I stop the preparations
for circumcision feast?
Don't, Ulgen.
Osman Bey considers it very important.
Continue the preparations.
Orhan Bey.
Alaaddin Bey.
I believe that my Bey is
the most powerful, the bravest...
...and the most self-sacrificing
among the beys.
If we, as his people, are worthy of
carrying his dreams to the far lands.
The sun of our nation will rise
in these lands, I hope.
I hope so. I hope so.
I hope so.
Now you speak, Orhan Bey.
We are the ones at the frontiers.
We are in the borders of the enemy.
Let the Anatolian Bey fight for the throne.
As long as we fight the heathens,
the men leaving the throne fight will join us.
Whether we go for the throne or not,
the conditions will push us to it.
Because we are the fighting ones.
Thank you.
My fellows. My brothers.
From the day...
when we buried my ancestor Suleyman Shah
in the wild water of Euphrates to this day,
...we have left no lands untouched
by our horses!
We were just a few before.
But we defeated many cruel ones!
We saw that capturing is easy.
But keeping...
Keeping it is the hardest.
Well, the Great Seljuks...
They collapsed in front of our eyes.
If only our state were strong and
we didn't have to talk about this today.
But we have to talk now.
For this reason,
both the fight and the feast will be ours.
See, hear and protect.
A new age has begun.
It will be hard,
but the new age will be ours.
The arrow is already off the bow.
The struggle to pick the Sultan of Turks has begun.
We will fight the cruel.
But if beys bring up troubles,
we will fight them too.
Alaaddin, arrive in Konya before the night.
-Hear Sultan Mesud. He'll give you the relics.
-As my Bey orders.
Orhan, there are some roving raiders
in the border of Byzantine.
This troubled times can bear no chaos.
Draw them to our side.
As my Bey orders.
-Boran. Tell Beys.
-My Bey.
I'll declare my decision at the feast in two days.
-As you order, my Bey.
-There is no going back.
The campaign is ours
and the victory belongs to Allah!
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too, my Bey. Welcome.
Praise be. It's a great molasses.
-It's boiled perfectly.
-Enjoy it, my Bey.
-Give some to the guests while opening the market.
-As you order, my Bey.
This frontier market that I'm building
will be the best market in these lands.
The poor and the rich...
All people will make us of it, if Allah permits.
-If Allah permits, my Bey.
Father, we've built the market with Allah's will.
You think everyone will come?
If you are asking about the beys,
they are all our kin, my daughter.
If you mean Osman Bey,
He will come too. Because the real purpose
of this market is to unite us.
-Father! Ambush!
-Alps! Stand on alert!
-Are you alright?
-I'm good.
There is Kayi seal on it.
-Osman did this! He'll pay for this!
-Give it to me.
Don't judge too quickly.
Osman did this, father!
Why would Osman do this?
What would he gain on my death?
My Bey, we got a message from Konya.
Sultan Mesud got poisoned.
-Now I've got my answer, Osman.
-What's going on, my Bey?
They poisoned Sultan Mesud.
Osman...
You got informed that
Sultan would die before I did.
So you tried to eliminate me, huh?
-My Bey, let me go to Yenisehir and destroy him.
-Never!
An open attack against someone
doing things secretly isn't clever.
I will make him pay for this.
But nobody will know about this ambush!
-Now hear me well! Gonca.
-My Bey.
Reach Konya before Sultan dies.
Make him seal a firman proving
that we are the true successor.
As my Bey father says.
Mehmet!
Osman who tried to hit us
must have sent messengers to gather beys.
Cross the way of those messengers!
-I want those beys with me!
-As my Bey father says.
Never hesitate on your missions.
If the soil craves blood, shed the blood!
-Inform Mehmus.
-As you order, my Bey.
Osman shot the first arrow. Now it's my turn.
Give me your blessings, Mother Malhun.
-You have it, my valiant.
Fatma told me that
you had a nightmare again.
Don't be sad, son. These days will be over too.
I sent a message to Sogut. Don't worry, alright?
-Thanks, mother.
-My mother.
-Give me your blessings.
-You have it, my lion.
Your mother is always here. Remember.
You boys have a safe journey. I'll pray for you.
-May Allah protect you.
-If Allah permits.
Ulgen prepared the food.
Don't forget to take it.
-Don't keep your father waiting. Come on.
-Son!.
-My Bey.
-My Orhan!
Praise be!
Son.
-May you have an open road and open eyes.
-Thank you, my father.
Taking The Bannerless to your side
will be tough. But I trust you.
With Allah's will, we'll be victorious.
We will.
My Alaaddin Ali.
My dear son.
Come here.
They put fire in Konya.
We don't know who is on whose side. Be cautious.
-Okay, father.
-Use this for entrance.
-Have a safe journey.
-Don't be worrying about me, dear father.
-I will do what's necessary.
-Thank you.
Come on.
-Well, brother.
-Brother.
May we have a safe journey.
-Come on.
-If Allah permits, brother. Come on.
Take care, sons.
Brothers, where are you going
without seeing me?
I am sending you alone now.
But in your next duty, I'll come with you!
-We are looking forward to that day, my sister.
-Don't I deserve it, my Bey father?
No... You have to defeat me in the training.
Then you can go.
Then when I come back,
we should exercise more, my sister.
Go fast, and come back fast, my brothers.
Come here...
Well...
Let's go.
Oi, oi.
Let's go, Malhun.
Malhun?
Why are you crying? Our valiants grew up.
They can take care of themselves now.
Regardless of that,
I cannot control my heart, my Bey.
Come on, wipe your tears.
They are both brave men,
they will come back soon.
If Allah permits.
Let's go, let's go.
-May it heal you.
-I had a dream.
May it be good.
In my dream...
...I was digging my Halime's grave.
Then Alaeddin came.
. I was dead, Kismet.
-Maybe the time has come, huh?
-How can you say that? May Allah protect you.
Besides, dreams never show the truth, they say.
Shahzade Alaeddin might need you now.
Do you think so?
You have to heal, Bala Hatun.
You have to heal for our Shahzade.
Look, your son is doing his best
to heal you.
Can I come in, Bala Hatun?
Something came from Yenisehir.
-Let her come.
-Come in.
May it be good, Inshallah.
Bala Hatun. Malhun Hatun sent this for you.
Healers in Yenisehir prepared it.
Thank her.
Tell me. How are things in the palace?
Osman, Alaeddin, Orhan?
-How are they?
-They are all good.
Shahzade(Prince) Alaeddin
went to Konya for a duty.
Sultan Mesud was poisoned.
They say he cannot recover.
Allah forbid...
Too much blood will be shed.
Too much blood.
Please contact us for any inquiries: turkision@gmail.com
Stay on alert!
We've fought many fights!
But the Bannerless are different!
Some of them are thieves,
some of them are murderers.
There are even those
who kill their own ancestors.
They don't show mercy to anyone!
Those leaderless people haven't seen you yet,
my Shahzade(Prince)
Those who kill their own fathers do not care
about anyone, Dark Ali. We have to be cautious.
They only care about each other.
Our duty is to stop them.
We will do what is necessary.
-Cerkutay! Cerkutay!
-They are going to cut me!
Sisters! Catch him! Cerkutay! Cerkutay!
Cerkutay come here!
If this Hatun catches me,
bad things will happen! Help me!
You little coward! Come here! I wonder
what Osman Bey would say if he saw you here!
My name is Cerkutay!
I am scared of nothing!
-Do you know Osman Bey? I want to talk to him.
Osman Bey, huh?
Everyone knows him here.
But be careful... Osman Bey is an angry man.
When you are talking to him, you have to
choose your words wisely. Or else...
-I have never heard that about him.
-Sure you haven't.
Those who witnessed
his anger never survived.
Protect your head.
Come on, you will be circumcised.
Sisters, take him. Cerkutay! -Let me go!
Let go off me!
I will not be circumcised! Fatma Hatun!
You will go to Osman when the time comes.
This is Cerkutay's amulet. You'll give it to him.
There's a feast in the hall.
There's nothing missing. The hungry ones are eating.
-Praise be, Praise be.
-People rejoiced when they heard you will join too.
As if everyone was waiting for this news.
We would want to make them happy with conquest,
but it was not destined to be for now.
Let's go to the ceremony
and let's comfort them a little.
If I wasn't here, you'd be leading the ceremony.
You wouldn't make them feel that I was missing.
-It wouldn't be the same.
-Of course not, you are my beautiful Hatun.
The sacrifices you have made so far
are countless.
You're not only the mother of my children,
you are the mother of the whole Kayi, thank you.
I was a daughter of a Bey. Now I'm the Hatun
of Osman Bey who will establish the holy state.
I'm ready to do whatever it takes,
and I will be so until my last breath.
See? That is why wherever I go,
I will not be worried.
Alps! Ambush! Get ready!
Allah is the Greatest.
-He is a tough fighter.
-I've seen many tough fighters.
I'll make him ask for mercy.
Ask for mercy.
Not before I die.
-Who are you? What are you looking for?
-I want to see your leader.
We don't have any leader,
we are united.
-Tell me your name.
-I'm Orhan Bey, son of Osman Bey.
You are the son of a Bey, is that so?
Your position is useless here, son of a Bey!
What does it take to enter, tell me.
Leave your Bey sword and position,
then you can enter through that door, son of Bey.
Do you want the sword of a man
that you just ambushed?
If you still determined despite the blood
that has been shed, your life is our trust, son of Bey.
Abandon your position and sword
so that we can listen to your problem.
I'm not going to be circumcised!
No!
-Bring the fugitive!
-I will not!
Don't wait like sacrificial lambs!
Run away! They will cut us all!
Attention!
Osman Bey!
-Peace be upon you
-Peace be upon you too.
-Save me my Bey!
-Cerkutay!
Come here, Cerkutay.
Son, you don't need to be afraid.
-I'll be your guardian.
-I'm not afraid of anything, my Bey.
-Is that so?
-I'm waiting for my father.
I don't want to be circumcised without him.
Is that so?
Then...
Look at me. I promise you as a Bey.
Let's postpone your circumcision
until your father arrives.
-Really, my Bey?
-Yes.
-Thank you Osman Bey!
Look here. Brave boy.
Long live Osman Bey!
-Long live Osman Bey!
-Astagfirullah. Thank you.
Come here. We will mount, draw swords
and we will conquer many lands together.
-If Allah permits, my Bey!
However, in order not to
stumble on our way...
...we need to have the
morals of Prophet.
We will not stop.
We will not let our sweat go cold.
If we walk our path with faith,
then you will see that our Creator
will expand our way.
-Tell me now, will you walk with me?
-We will, my Bey!
-Will you walk with me?
-We will my Bey!
Praise be, praise be!
Thanks to my Mighty Creator
for making me a Bey of a people like you.
May my Creator make you
the Bey of all the ummah.
-May Allah keep you with us Osman Bey!
-Long live Osman Bey!
Thank you. Come on then,
let's start the ceremony.
Come on, let our soul be rejoiced.
Boran.
-Yes, my Bey.
-Let the words come out.
As you order, my Bey.
The silver streams of paradise
They flow and sing, “Allah, Allah!”
The nightingales of Islam arise
and sing aloud, “Allah, Allah!”
With faces brighter than the moon,
With voices sweet they all commune.
The heavenly maidens sing this tune,
"Glory to Allah, Glory to Allah!"
The one who is in love with The Righteous
Their tears drop down.
They are clear inside and outside.
They sing: "Allah!"
Ask The Righteous for whatever you ask.
Take His way.
Nightangle is in love with rose.
It sings: "Allah, Allah!"
Yunus Emre has this to say,
We’ll meet together on that day,
Where songbirds sing and fountains play,
So sing with me: “Allah, Allah!”
What a meaningful thing this is.
Thanks to Allah, He made us listen to this.
We listened to many songs,
but none of them was like this.
-Boran.
-My Bey.
-Tell me who spoke these words that strike our hearts.
-No one heard his voice nor saw his face, my Bey.
They call him Lover Yunus.
One of the followers of Taptuk Emre.
O Praise be!
Praise be!
He spoke the words coming
out of his heart, Lover Yunus. Praise be!
Let's go.
Fame is a disaster, fame is a disaster. It really is.
My Bey.
A trader wants to see you. That one.
Let's go before we die,
before the dagger of heathens reaches us,
Before a girl falls in love with us,
hit it Bannerless, hit it!
-Hit! Hit! Hit!
-A Bannerless does not show mercy in the field.
No one is braver than them.
When the swords are taken out, the field is hell.
Before the arrow of death hits us,
hit Bannerless, hit!
Hit! Hit! Hit! Hit! Hit!
-Tell me now, son of Bey. What brought you here.
-I'm here for an invitation.
The nightmare of the cruel,
the hope of the innocent...
the glorious Bey of Kayi tribe, Osman Bey...
invites you to be the Ghazis behind him.
To what? To be a ghazi?
-Don't talk nonsense, son of Bey.
-Our cause is gold.
Our cause is coin, what will you
and your father will give us?
Without the soul of holy war,
what's the point of having treasures?
What's better than being a ghazi
for a valiant?
Look at those behind me. Look at them!
They spent their lives in dungeons.
Half of them are fugitives...
The rest are leftovers.
They don't even know how many
they have killed so far.
Tell me Atmaca,
how many people have you killed?
If I am to count, the number would
be the dark spots in my beard.
This is the army of leaderless.
This is the guild of Bannerless.
Our purpose is to have treasure.
If your goal is not the holy war,
even your swords abhor you.
Such a pity.
Look at the boy. His father gave him Alps and horse,
and gave him a sword, and he despises the Bannerless!
I...
shed my blood for what I have.
-What sufferings did you endure, son of Bey?
-Do you think I was born to be in a palace?
I grew up on horse, in battlefields.
If you want to test me,
then show me the field.
You're a lucky man Orhan Bey.
Caravan is in our range.
Come on. Let's see your talent.
Come on.
Tell me, what's the issue?
Osman Bey.
-How can I tell you.
-Stop babbling, trader. Just tell me.
Cerkutay, your man who has been missing
for a long time, I know where he is.
Cerkutay is missing since Iznik.
If you lie, I'll cut your tongue.
I am telling you the truth, Osman Bey.
Stop there!
From now on, choose your words wisely.
Osman Bey... I am trading with Lefka.
I heard that a Turk was captured in
Lefka from one of the commanders
They tortured him.
They tried to make him speak.
But he kept saying the same thing.
"I will cut you into pieces
with my double swords!"
My brother...
One day, he bit one of the commanders'
ear off when they were torturing him.
-They stabbed him on his heart, but he didn't die.
-My valiant's heart is strong.
-It's Cerkutay. Cerkutay..
-My Bey, let me go and take my brother.
No... Stop. What is this then?
-I took it from a trader,
they said it belonged to Cerkutay.
We will take Cerkutay.
I won't leave my valiant there.
Or else, I will destroy Lefka.
And we were going to reward the one who
brought news from my valiant with gold.
Give it to him.
I didn't inform you for gold, Osman Bey.
To make a big business agreement with you...
We will reward the one who brought news
from our beloved one for sure... Don't worry. But...
If you are lying, then
I will cut your tongue off, know that.
Get ready. Bayindir. Bring Cerkutay's gold.
We will either take him by talking,
or our swords will talk.
Yes my Bey.
Mehmus! You will come with us too.
-Good news, Ulgen sister! Good news!
-Stop, my daughter. Do not say it right away.
What is good news? Malhun Hatun?
-Is it Cerkutay?
-Cerkutay! Cerkutay Bey is alive!
Is he?
I know he is alive! I knew it!
-My Allah... Thanks to You, my Creator...
-Finally, Ulgen.. Finally.
My Cerkutay... Your father is coming!
Your father is alive! My Cerkutay is alive!
My father is coming, huh?
Food! Food!
Give us food!
He will come, my son... He will come.
Your father is alive, I know, Cerkutay is alive.
Lefka Castle
Germiyanogullari Border
My Bey...
Mehmus convinced Osman.
Osman is going to his cage.
Inform Beys.
We drew the bow,
now it is time to shoot the arrow.
Yes my Bey.
Forgive me, my Bey, but..
We are walking to Lefka.
We are just a group of men.
May Allah forbid, what if they set a trap?
Bayindir Bey, we have been searching
for Cerkutay for a long time.
But we haven't heard from my valiant.
We sent news everywhere.
We checked every dungeon.
But... now we will go there, even if it is a trap.
Who said we were not crowded?
Boran.
My Bey... The pigeon must've arrived in Sogut.
Our Alps in Sogut are getting
ready to follow us.
-Alps! We will spend the night in Sogut.
-Yes my Bey.
Come on! Come on! Go!
He is coming.
You will never see the Beys, you messenger.
Beys can only talk to my father.
Take this messenger. He'll be our guest for a long time.
-Did you catch the messengers
for the others beylics, Gokmen?
We're holding all the ways
. We'll let nobody pass, for sure.
Mehmet Bey, I have important news for you.
Go ahead, Atmaca.
Someone else would take all the gold
you have for this crucial information.
-Speak and let me value your information.
-A soldier come to the bannerless guild today.
Orhan, son of Osman.
He wanted to take The Bannerless beside him.
-What did The Bannerless say?
-They haven't said anything yet.
A caravan is coming from Constantinople.
They'll attack it together.
After that, they will decide.
You gave me valuable information.
Your value is rising day by day, Atmaca.
Gokmen!
My Shahzade(Prince).
Let's go and spoil Orhan's plan.
Alps, let's go!
Surround it!
Save the princess!
Holofira.
Orhan.
What are you doing here?
You've proved to be tough, son of Bey!
You are skilled.
Wow! Wow!
Orhan Bey caught a pretty prey!
What are they doing here?
My Shahzade(Prince),
Germiyanids came here before us.
Our mission will be harder than we thought.
Be cautious.
Sure.
Alaaddin Bey, son of Osman Bey.
-I'm here to see Mighty Sultan.
I'm Gonca Hatun, daughter of Germiyanoglu Yakup Bey
We're supposed to see Mighty Sultan first.
Mighty Vizier gave strict orders.
We'll let nobody see Sultan Mesud for his safety.
Mighty Sultan invited us personally.
This is his letter.
Healers are with our Sultan right now, Alaaddin Bey.
We'll host you until Sultan Mesud is available.
Let me take you to your room, Gonca Hatun.
You'll take me to Sultan Mesud's chamber
when the dark falls.
Stay back, Beys.
This hatun is mine.
You wanted to see how I fight
and you saw it.
We believed in your war skills,
son of Bey. Eyvallah(Alright) but...
Both the hostages and bounties are ours.
-You are just a guest here.
-I and this hatun have a history.
-I want no words against this!
-She won't be harmed.
We'll send a message to her house and
deliver her safely when we get the gold.
Don't act against our law.
If you bring the gold, you get the hatun.
I want no words anymore!
My Shahzade(Prince),
we will fight to the end.
We came here to take The Bannerless
on our side, not to break them.
Our mission is clear. We can't open another
front to fight while there is chaos in our lands.
She won't be harmed even slightly.
She won't be! Tie her up!
You won't touch her!
I thought you were a Bey.
But it seems you are a ravager.
When we get out of here safely,
I'll tell you everything, daughter of Lord.
-You won't leave me alone with these, right?
-I'll come back for you, Holofira.
-Be patient.
-Don't leave me here.
I'm talking to you, Orhan. Don't you leave me here!
Don't be afraid. Come on.
Dark Ali! Go to Yenisehir quickly.
-Bring a chest of gold from my share.
-As you order, my Shahzade.
Come on!
We dreamed about this day a lot within
the cold walls of the monastery.
If you want peace,
..prepare for the war.
We'll set the fire of riot among them!
-Tell me about Karacahisar.
-Christian people are uneasy in Karacahisar.
The sparks of riot are about to turn into a fire.
-Tell me about Sogut.
-Merchants in Sogut are uneasy.
The fire of riot will burn over them.
The wind to grow the fire is Sultan Mesud
that I personally poisoned!
I sent the message to Osman.
You shot the Kayi arrow to Yakup.
They will fight each other.
The fire will grow bigger and be their disaster!
As we burn them,
each Christian will take courage!
-For Christ!
-For Christ! For Christ! For Christ!
Increase your numbers in the cities and castles!
Reach everyone! Find trustworthy men!
Sow the seeds of riot in Christian hearts!
When Turks fight each other,
...we'll start the riot in tribes,
citadels and cities!
Be ready. Here we go.
Bala.
Bala. Bala.
Bala! Bala! My Bala!
My Bala..
Osman!
Osman what are you doing? Go, go away!
Go! Go! -I won't go!
Go, it will pass on!
-No, I won't go.
Osman, I will pass on the disease!
-I won't go anywhere, Bala!
Go! -Don't!
Bala...
-Osman...
-My Halime...
My heart's fire..
My Halime...
Halime..
This wound will never heal, Osman.
Never.
Of course it won't close up...
...but we will get used to it.
We will get used to it, my Bala. We will.
But I think you seem alright.
You seem better. You are alright, right?
I am. I am alright.
But you don't seem alright, my Osman.
No... I am alright. I am.
Besides, I have good news for you.
It's not enough but it'll feel better. Cerkutay..
You know, we hadn't heard from him for a while..
We've heard from him.
We had been looking for him.
We heard that he was in Lefka.
Now we will go to save my valiant.
Thanks to Allah... Thanks to Allah, my Osman.
May Allah let him come together with his child.
May his child come together with him.
Now tell me.
Now I am waiting for your good news!
Tell me. The cure Alaeddin brought from India...
It helped you, right?
-It did.
It works. I am feeling better than before,
don't worry.
You are telling me the good news,
but you are hiding the bad ones, my Osman.
I heard about Sultan Mesud.
There will be a fight, right?
There is always a fight, my Bala.
We are trying to stop the fight.
Don't worry about this. Don't.
Bala... Are you alright? Huh?
Go out! -Are you feeling alright?
Go, Osman! Go away! -Let me give you some water.
Here, here, drink some water.
Drink this water.
Hatuns! Kismet Hatun! Come and see her!
Bala..
Drink it, drink! May it heal you.
-Get out, Osman.
-Bala..
-Go. Get out Osman!
-My Bala!
-Go!
-I won't go, my Bala!
Go, Osman!
What is that?
You said you were better...
-You said you were better..
-I am.
My Bala, what is this?
Tell me!
What is this?
It's better than before. I am alright.
Don't worry about me.
Pour it here.
If you don't want to sleep,
cover your nose and mouth.
Come on!
In the name of Allah...
We cannot oppose to our Bey's order.
We will do as Osman Bey orders. Baysungur...
Soldier disguise.
-Yes my Shahzade.
No one can stop me from doing my duty.
If they put something in my way,
it is my duty to get rid of it.
They say he fights in the morning,
studies during the night.
So Alaeddin is a scholar, huh?
They say Osman Bey values his opinions
although he is the little brother.
They say his intelligence is
his most cruel weapon.
We will see whose sword is more cruel.
Can I come in, Gonca Hatun?
Come in.
Guardians will switch after healers leave.
Then I will take you to our Sultan,
Gonca Hatun.
What about Osman's son? Alaeddin?
-We cannot let him see the Sultan.
-He won't be able to see the Sultan.
Now he is in his room.
Soldiers are waiting at his door.
When the sun rises, we will send him
with empty hands.
The scholar man who you said was intelligent
turned out to be stupid.
Let him wait.
Resist, Holofira...
Resist. Be patient.
Turahan Alp.
-When Dark Ali brings the gold, we will set out.
-Yes, my Shahzade(Prince).
The bulgur in stew is ready, Orhan Bey.
In the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
It's so delicious.
Come on brave boys, take a seat.
Why would you turn halal into haram,
Mehmed Bey?
We would share our food
if you asked.
Only the incapable ones ask for something,
Orhan Bey. We take what we want without asking.
Today, it's just bulgur stew.
What will you want in the future?
Let us know so we can hide it.
What do you even have?
Two castles and two tribes.
What you have is like a gift
we give to our sergeants.
Innkeeper!
Bring ayran to Mehmed Bey.
It seems our conquests made him dry.
Let him cool off.
We do not set eyes on them.
We always be happy with
the victories of our minors.
The purpose of our struggle
is not to be great.
Our every move is for the holy war.
But since you are happy about it,
we will make you even more happier.
Welcome Mehmed Bey
in a way that is worthy of his might.
Orhan Bey!
We'll see each other again.
I know very well why the gold is here.
You will see the might when the sun rises.
Follow me Gonca Hatun,
I'll take you inside through the hidden door.
What's this, brother?
In the name of Allah...
Sultan Mesud.
My Sultan.
My Osman Bey is deeply sad
due to your situation.
We set out as soon as we heard about it.
-I'm at your command. I'll do whatever
it takes for you to heal... -I've been...
...dead for a long time.
-My Sultan.
-Get closer. Closer.
Inside of the pillow,
there is a map. Take that map.
What's this map for, my Sultan?
The treasure.
The treasure of Seljuks.
I've been piling it up outside for a long time.
Now it belongs to Osman Bey.
Water. Water.
Alaeddin Bey.
My Sultan.
Give your earnings to the needy's call,
No matter how long you live,
death awaits us all.
For those who see the path unfolds,
I have mercy for the ants, and all the souls.
Are you hungry?
You are hungry.
If my ancestor is Hadrat Suleyman,
The ant that asked for a wheat
from him is your ancestor.
It means your food is in my bag.
They belong to others.
The One Who crossed our paths
will take what's in my bag to you.
He will for sure.
Those who look but cannot see are coming.
Dervish Effendi, what are you standing on the path.
Don't you see that we are in a hurry?
Everyone walks towards their destinations.
It is the same for you and for these creatures.
Dervish Effendi.
Boran. Hold on.
What lives are you talking about?
Not me. The Righteous mentions in Holy Quran.
He says
"O ants! Go quickly into your homes,
so Solomon and his armies do not crush you,
unknowingly." [Surah An-Naml - 27:18]
The Righteous protects His living beings
even from Hadrat Suleyman.
Protect the ants, Bey.
Let them reach their destinations.
You are so right, Dervish effendi.
This path belongs to the ants.
-Thank you. You showed us the right thing to do.
-Astagfirullah.
Alps. We'll go this way.
Let's not be unfair to the ants.
Okay my Bey.
The one who sees what we don't see,
the one who shows it to us...
Tell us your name Dervish Efendi.
We escape from our name,
but you question us about what we escape.
Just assume this poor man
is a helpless Dervish.
- Thank you.
Come on! Go!
And you are running
to the thing you should escape.
Come on!
A way with a far range who shall arrive?
A way with countless troubles, who shall achieve?
Preparation for the journey is needed,
it needs a little and it needs more...
It takes an iron heart to enter this steep path.
There are many
who can deceive others on this path...
The disgrace of those
who follow their nafs will never go away.
Know that there are seventy thousand soldiers
who fight for appearance on this path...
Only a man who killed his nafs can
defeat those soldiers with his wrath...
My father will be very happy
after he finds out that we succeeded.
Sultan Mesud closed his worldly eyes
and opened his eyes on the other side!
Sultan Mesud closed his worldly
eyes and opened his eyes on the other side!
Attention! The Protector of all Turks...
...the protector of the poor,
the enemy of the cruel, the provider of justice...
...the Sultan of Anatolia and nearby cities,
Germiyanogullari Bey, Yakup Bey!
What Sultan?
Where did this come from?
Now we'll see why we are here.
- Peace be upon you.
- Peace be upon you too.
You must be wondering
why Yakup Bey gathered you.
We are, Yakup Bey.
But we are more wondering what your aide said.
We seek the good in every evil Mubarizeddin,
son of Esref.
I got the message about Sultan Mesud.
He's in his deathbed.
The sun of state is sinking in Konya.
Our land is about to surrender
to a dark night.
Terrible. Terrible.
The sun will rise for the enemy, huh?
Neither the sun will for the enemy
nor will our sun of state sink!
Beys, we are here for this reason.
As Konya surrendered to Mongolians,
...Sultan of Turks will be one the beys of Anatolia!
Who will lead?
That's why I got called myself Sultan!
I put myself in to lead the homeland.
These lands won't remain without a head!
Now I'm asking you, the great beys of Turkmen!
Are you with me in my decision?
We are, we will.
-We're with you, Yakup Bey.
-We are with you, Yakup Bey.
We're with you, Yakup Bey.
The messenger must have left, my Bey.
-Come on then. We should leave too.
-Okay.
The seal has been impressed.
The firman must be on the way.
When the firman arrives,
all the beys will kiss my hand.
But him first.
Guard! Tell your Lord...
Osman Bey, Great Bey of Kayi,
Protector of all Turkmen, is here. Come on!
If you want to take the hostage,
you have to leave your swords, bows and horses!
We will never leave our horses!
-Leave the bows and horses.
-As my Bey orders. Come on.
Open the gate!
-Lord Zenon.
-To what do we owe this visit, Osman Bey?
They say you're holding
my warrior Cerkutay.
I'll give you as much gold as you want.
Now give me Cerkutay nicely.
Bring the gold.
Here is the gold for my warrior.
I don't want to shed blood.
Bring Cerkutay.
Bring him.
Cerkutay. Cerkutay.
Cerkutay.
-Cerkutay!
-Cerkutay, my brother.
-He's alive.
-Thanks to Allah, my Bey.
I will get you out of here.
I will get you out.
It's enough! Your man will stay here
and you will die here. Soldiers!
-My Bey! My Bey!
-Cerkutay! Cerkutay!
-Protect the Bey! My Bey!
-Cerkutay!
-Cerkutay! Cerkutay!
-My Bey! My Bey!
Cerkutay!
You... You... Mehmus
So what now? Son of Bey
didn't come to take you, huh?
I'll punish that son of Bey and you!
Greedy animals!
I'll choke you with that gold you want!
This woman turned out to be
a crazy one, brother.
Someone's coming!
-Peace be upon you
-Orhan Bey!
I guess your horse is lame!
You came pretty quick(!)
Dark Ali.
It's better to keep it short,
the gold is here.
I want the Hatun!
-Look what he says. He "wants the Hatun"
As if he is not the one
who attacked my caravan. Marauder.
Do you think we would give the
Hatun to you with so little gold, son of Bey?
Who do you think you're giving?
I'm not a slave!
I'll make you all pay for this.
You came all the way here for nothing.
Someone else took her before you.
Do you hear what you say Beys?
She is mine!
I won't give her to anyone.
Orhan Bey.
What did I tell you?
I take what I want without telling it.
I took her.
This Hatun...
is now mine.
Lord! It was a trap, is that so?
Come on!
My Alps.
My valiants.
Drop your sword and surrender, Osman.
Otherwise I'll throw
the heads of your alps to you.
We do not have any soldier
behind us that are afraid to die!
Come on, Lord! Come on!
Osman Bey.
You attacked our castles,
you brought your men to our citadels.
You despised Byzantium, Osman.
-Now you have lost.
-The time will decide who will lose.
Why are you keeping us alive, why?
So, they are coming.
These Beys are here to save you from me.
Be thankful to them, Osman.
Otherwise, only your dead body
would be able to leave here.
Soldiers.
Lord Zenon, the owner of Lefka.
You listened to me and didn't touch my Bey.
Yakup Bey, son of Germiyanoglu,
if you didn't send your messenger
-Only Osman's dead body would be...
-Never!
Never, Lord.
Osman Bey is one of my most precious Beys.
Would you be alive if he was hurt?
You stopped because you thought what would happen to you.
If an arrow hits one of us,
all of us would bleed, Lord.
Osman Bey, thankfully your captivity
has ended, Thank Allah.
Welcome among us.
White dove has just brought the dark news.
Sultan Mesud passed away.
-May Allah forgive his sins.
-Amin.
Thank you. Long live.
You saved us from the oppressors
may Allah bless you.
Thank you. I owe you my life.
Would I ever leave you behind, Osman Bey?
Your swords will not be sheathed
before you shed each other's blood.
We're beginning now.
From now on
I'm the Sultan of all the Beys in Anatolia.
All of the Beys told that they are behind me.
and that they would walk with me.
Now it's your turn.
Declare your loyalty, kiss my hand, Osman Bey.
We don't want to walk behind
the one that follows the path of The Righteous.
Instead, we want to walk side by side.
Please contact us for any inquiries: turkision@gmail.com